I am in the fifth poorest country in the world.
here most people live
with less than a dollar a day.
and here the kitchen.
but what I see on the street is not just poverty,
is talent,
it's music,
something no money
can buy.
Thanks man,
Valeu bro!
I like you bro
but still
lack of opportunity
and that's why I decided to do a different challenge.
my idea is
produce the biggest talent show in this city
and award the winner
with twenty thousand meticais.
welcome to mozambique!
and that challenge starts now.
talent show there,
Or twenty thousand meticais!
who wants to do the talent show there?
Talent show!
who knows how to dance,
sing,
agree with prize of twenty thousand meticais?
can sing?
can't sing,
dance, rap?
Thanks,
We are there!
but what's hardest for me is choosing the place,
otherwise I'm doing
promote a talent show and I have nothing.
but it will work.